jack
джек
god good evening somewhere it’s cold you there the
бог добрый вечер где то холоду вас там
floor there is the most popular republic,
этаж там самая народная республика на
it seems to me that the lawyer who is to
мне кажется у юрист который это
work out the collectors and summer
отрабатывать коллекторов и летние
I am the one who works out the
я и есть который отрабатываю русских чат
Russians  I’m asking the people of Russia
вообще посмотрите на я у людей россии
how do you feel about the war in
спрашиваю как вы относитесь к войне в
Ukraine,
украине
I’m sure you will see to the rescue
я уверен вы увидите на выручку
they all immediately freeze there hot it’s
они все сразу там морозятся горячую это
not a war, well, what do
не война ну что вы у
you have, it’s just officially called
вас просто официально она называется
special operations of a specially military operation
спецопераций специально военной операции
NATO war
нато война
Yes, we are very negatively very, but
да мы очень отрицательно очень а вот
now I had guys, here are the Ukrainian
сейчас у были ребята вот украинские
military, I’m just talking to them
военные я просто вот с ними я говорю
guys, take care of yourself and your loved ones
ребят берегите себя и своих близких
that once again you think it’s wrong
что еще раз вы считаете что неправильно
Dasha ordered and rock the wedge, I think it’s
даша велено и скалу клина я считаю что
wrong when
неправильно когда
it was Donetsk today
сегодня было
understood
понимали
our cages people these are Ukrainian children in
наши клетки люди это украинские дети в
Donetsk
донецке
let’s  tell me when the
давайте расскажите мне когда началась
war in the Donbass began
война на донбассе
in 2014 on what date  what
в 2014 в какого числа какого что какого
date is
числа
April 12 the world for April 12, let's say
12 апреля мир за 12 апреля давайте так
12 you know the dates correctly until
12 вы правильно даты знаете до 12-го
April 12, Russian militants Girkin and
апреля российские боевики гиркин и
company came and captured the city
компания так пришли и захватили город
glorious yes yes, that is, these terrorists
славен да да то есть эти террористы
captured the city began to terrorize the
захватили город начали терроризировать
population kill the population this is where
население убивать население вот с этого
the military began  actions in the Donbass,
начались военные действия на донбассе
after that, the National Security and Defense Council met in the evening
после этого вечером собралась совет
and
национальной безопасности и обороны и
decided to start the otitis of the
приняли решение о начале отите
Russian operation, which officially
российской операции которые официально
in 2 days
через 2 дня
tell me so tell me at least one
назовите мне так назовите мне хоть одну
victim of this conflict until March 12 whom
жертву этого конфликта до 12 марта кого
Ukraine
убила украина до 12 12 апреля
killed before April 12  but
до захвата соляру танки пошли по же
tanks have been walking around for 91 years,
танки у нас 91 года ходит
wait said andrey andrey here is andrey
подожди сказал андрей
tanks when they went towards the
вот андрей танки когда пошли в сторону
donbass sense 100 but they were in the
донбасса смысле 100 но они были на
donbass from 91 on calls from all of
донбассе с 91 года на звонки с их всех
those
тех этих
first 1 first victim when under the wheels
первую 1 первую жертву когда под колеса
say again here you are  now,
скажите еще раз вот у вас сейчас
for example, from Yakutia there, from Buryatia, tanks were
например из якутии там из бурятии танки
transported, for example, to the eastern and
перевозились например в восточную и
western parts of Russia
западную часть россии
maybe here they are, maybe that’s how
возможно вот они возможно так и есть так
it is, that is, if the burrow doesn’t have it, of
то есть если у норы нет так не было
course, there weren’t similar wine ones here they were transported to
конечно подобных винных сюда перевезли
translate scanavi you wouldn’t have your
переводить сканави у вас там бы нет ваши
tanks from Russian there, they can
танки от российский может расти
only grow in a bar, so look like we
только были в баре так смотрите такие у
have for
нас для
see this is the armed forces of ukraine
смотрите это вооруженные силы украины
they are on the territory of the state
они находятся на территории государства
ukraine commit state 22 march yes
украина соверши государстве 22 мар да
they went where they went 2014 yes
они пошли куда куда пошли 2014 да пошли
they went they went to the side where to
они они пошли в сторону куда сторону
the side to the side of the border correctly
куда в сторону границы правильно потому
because we already have
что у нас уже смотреть e27 26 февраля
to watch  the military
был захвачен в и российским военным
Parliament of Crimea the Cabinet of Ministers of Crimea is
парламент крыма кабинет министров крыма
so official in the middle of the document, from
так официальный посреди документа на с
that moment Russia’s invasion of
этого момента началось вторжение россии
coals
в угли
began, wait and start saying, I listened to you, of
подождите и начали говорю я вас слушал
course, that the state of Ukraine is
естественно что государство украина так
transferring military units from one place
переводит воинские части с одного места
to another so no one
в другое так никто не какие там против
used tanks against the inhabitants of Donbass  so
жители донбасса танки не использовал так
there wasn’t even anything like that so it was
не было даже ничего такого так там
calm there in the Donbass
спокойно на донбассе было те времена
but to the border, yes, in order to strengthen the
но на границу да для того чтобы укрепить
border, because an invasion from the border was expected
границу потому что ожидалось вторжение с
so Russian and on April 12, so
границы так российское и 12 апреля так
Russian militants crossed the border and
российские боевики перешли границу так и
began to capture cities before that, before
начали захватывать города до этого до 12
April 12, name me at least one victim as the
апреля назовите мне хоть одну жертву как
Ukrainian regime, who is behind whom there with a
украинского режима кто за кого там
tank if  I confess that I was wrong
танком если я признаюсь что я был неправ
tell me you can google it
назовите мне можете погуглить
so [ __ ] but there is in youtube
так что говнеца но есть в youtube
if such and such a person would already be promoted by
если такой был уже бы распиарить
such and such a person
такого-то и такого-то человека
so tell me take a multi tell
так скажите возьмите по мульти скажите
me who to find what surname
мне кого найти какую фамилию
any no date when the
какую-никакую дату когда
tanks enter
заход танков
before  April 12, so what kind of tanks
до 12 этого апреля так какие танки если
if Russian militants just came there with
там российские боевики просто пришли с
grenade launchers and with small arms
гранатометами и со стрелковым оружием
seized the department in English,
захватили отделение по-английски не
please, Andrey, in which city of
пожалуйста андрей в каком города
Khmelnitsky
хмельницкий
I am now, this is all [ __ ], this is going
я его сейчас это вся все [__] это идет
here, we are ordinary people, too, not a military man, there is
вот мы обычные люди тоже не военный есть
some  way out of this situation we can
какой-то выход из этой ситуации мы можем
we can somehow influence you
мы можем как-то повлиять ты
will talk about it now all
об этом поговорим сейчас прошло еще все
this garbage has passed  see how you can
это [__] заварила смотрите как можно
influence in the first place, here you, as citizens of the
повлиять во первых вот вы как граждане
Russian Federation, should stop
российской федерации должны перестать
supporting this, because while the
поддерживать это потому что пока
citizens of the Russian Federation were, it was
граждане российской федерации были это
Ukraine that bombed something there, of
украина там что-то бомбила так само себя
course, the Russian government will
конечно российская власть будет
continue this war and it becomes like this to me
продолжать эту войну и она так мне
if there is support in the
становится если есть поддержка в
Russian  in society, well, you understand, no, in
российском обществе ну понимаете нет в
Russian society there is a lot of dust
российском обществе очень много пыли
measurements that are immediately taken to the camp, yes,
замеров которых сразу сейчас в лагерь да
but look, here you are now sitting, here is your
но смотри вот вы сейчас сидите вот ваш
colleague, look, it’s you who bombed Ukrainians in this,
коллега вид это же вы там бомбили в этом
so further,
убивали украинцы так дальше совершенно
what’s the situation now, the
какая сейчас ситуация
way out can well shake that people have stopped
выход хоро может раскачать что перестали
dying  yes, that is, look for this,
гибнуть люди да то есть смотри для этого
it is necessary for russia to withdraw troops from
надо чтобы россия вывела войска из
ukraine
украины
as ordinary people can
как обычные люди могут
hope 1 so you have to stop
надежду 1 так вы должны перестать это
supporting poland for yourself here is your
для себя поддерживать польшу вот ваш
colleague he supports this he
коллега он поддерживает этого ему
succeeds but the same will always be
получается но такой же всегда будет
allowable some percentage from some
допустим какой-то процент со какой-то
about the correct data, but before the majority
про правильно данных же до большинство
for so the power acts, but if
за так власть действует а если бы
more  nstvo people of Russia did not support
большинство людей россии не поддерживала
in Belarus were to most people does not
в беларуси были к большинству людей не
support it categorically not
поддерживает это категорически не
but gave a version with Belarusians communicated
а дал версия с белорусами общался так
so no one is found who says that
вот никто не находится кто говорит что
he is a form howled and therefore before it was not
он это форма завыл и поэтому до было не
good you are good you can interrupt
давай хорошо вы вы хорошо можно перебью
but try
а попробуй
well here  we are an occupier there
хорошо вот мы там оккупант
why is the packaging Kherson what is the
почему упаковки херсон каков к
Russian troops occupied by the head of
оккупированной оголовком российские
the
войска
blow let’s also stand on the dam there in the
удар давайте тоже на дамбе там стоят в
radiator weren’t merlini you’ll die
радиатор не был мерлини погибнешь твари
non-military creatures don’t die but copper ones are also
не военного не погибает а медные тоже
yes well the result is because of which
есть да ну результатом из-за чего
invincible due to the fact that the aggressor
непобедимой из-за того что агрессор за
attacked  for example, let's do this when hitler
напал например давайте так когда гитлер
attacked the soviet union of the soviet drying
напал на советский союз советских сушка
up to liberated the cities, the civilians
до освобождал города погибали мирные
also
тоже
understood come on yes yes and the guilty one was
понимали давай да да а виноватый кто был
the soviet union or hitler-hitler
в этом советский союз или гитлер-гитлер
about because he unleashed a war and the
про потому что он развязал войну а
secular ones
светские можно
can also be about kakhovka itself so if that  there is
так же сама про каховку так если то есть
if ukraine liberates its cities
если украина освобождает своих городах
to act correctly correctly the
на действует правильно правильно
soviet union was liberated and this year
советский союз освобождался и года это
right, ukraine is being built and gerda is
правильно украина сооружается и герда то
wrong
неправильно
as a bran, but from hitler the soviet union
как бран а вот от гитлера советский союз
liberated its own to the end normally,
освобождал своего до торца нормально
maybe i stalin’s edge before it was smashed
может я сталин грани до его раз разнесли
to shreds and the
в клочья и
soviet troops and that the soviet troops
советские войска и что советские войска
defended their city
оборонялись свой город
d’andrea the ukrainian people for an hour, like, they
d'andrea украинский народ час ну типа
say to support  our president for
говорит поддерживать свой президент
any purpose, that is, we liberate these
любыми целями то есть освобождаемся эти
territories only then finish when
территории только потом закончить когда
Russia dumps all the lands the rest, and with
россия свалит все земли осталь да при
such we lay out ordinary people -
таких раскладываем обычные люди - вреда
people don’t want harm here, when even before
люди не хотят вот у нас когда еще до
this invasion there were different opinions,
этого вторжение разные были мнения так
so now I’m watching the absolute 1
то сейчас вот я наблюдаю абсолютку 1
you will become like  you want to say that
станешь как это вы хотите сказать что
Hitler didn’t carry around Stalingrad to inflicted
гитлер не носил по сталинграду к наносил
Tallinn city before the bombing of Hitler’s city and
гитлера таллин град и
he said today not only
говорил он сегодня не лишь 10 раз
I repeat 10 times and the
повторю и
Soviet troops when they liberated the
советские войска когда освобождали
cities
города
bombarded the
бомбардировали
Soviet
советская
artillery how they knocked the Germans out of the
артиллерия как они выбивали немцев из
city and the
города и
bombing Yes,
бомбардировками да
well, how and how the Germans  either they themselves left
ну как а как немцы сами ушли
or
или
Andrew there are some layouts
андрей здесь есть какие-то расклады
here  yes, from above and a shadow, that’s the thing, it’s
когда сверху и тень вот вещь это сегодня
already the third time today to ask when the premises will end
уже третий спрашивать когда закончится
, as if I know when la
помещений как бы вот я знаю когда la
finish no one knows, that is, this is
закончить никто не знаю то есть это
such a thing that no one can predict
такая вещь которая никто не спрогнозирую
so it will end in the fall or it can
так она уже закончится осенью а может
drag on for a year or two, absolutely no
затянуться на год на два абсолютно никто
one knows  it depends on how
не знаю это зависит от того насколько
much Western aid to Ukraine will
западной помощь украине будет сильно чем
be stronger than it will be stronger the faster it will
она будет сильнее тем быстрее будет
grow squeezed out, for example, they only
расти выдавливаться вот например лишь
squeezed out the Scythian Chernigov and Sumy Kharkiv already there, they
выдавили уже там
gave out the barbaric that Russia
выдали варварское что россию просто
simply conceded and left
уступил и ушла не просто уступила ей
Chersonesos they are now giving bombs now
херсонеса они сейчас дают бомбы сейчас
Mariupol is also far from Mariupol there is no
мариуполю тоже далеко не мариуполе нет
Mariupol in why
мариуполе в на зачем
andrey answer yes why do you hit your own
андрея ответа да зачем вы по своим же
prisoners of war heroes look yes
военнопленным ударюсь heroes смотрите да
it is very such a foot once bars
это очень такой ступни когда-то бруски
feature of Russian propaganda so the Russians
фишка российской пропаганды так россияне
killed our prisoners of war like this and
убили наших военнопленных так и
furnishes it that  ukraine hit
обставляет это что украина ударила по
its prisoner of war hummer itself but
своим военнопленный хаммер сам но
for some reason  I don’t show where these
почему-то не показываю там где эти
fragments were shown you noticed where you
осколки показали вы заметили где
showed your son’s highmore there
показали хаймор сына какой-то лавочке
are fragments from hammers in some shop and they were put up
лежат осколки от hammers а их поставили
yes why not show if you
да почему не показать если вы пригласили
would invite international observers glide
бы международных наблюдателей glide вот
look behind
смотрите за
but
но
[music]
[музыка]
someone didn’t invite them yes yes  yes, that is, it
кто-то их не пригласил да да да то есть
turns out that the lift will be swept away, Russia has not yet been invited,
получается сметет лифт не пригласили еще
so Russia has
россия так россия сделала
committed an international war crime by
международное военное преступление так
killing and what killed you now, they are
убив причем чем там убилась ты сейчас
sorting it out, as if
разбираются так как бы конкретно
there are already specialists, even I will look at the
специалисты уже есть даже я посмотрю
Russian military, these bloggers, too, and
российских военных этих блогеров тоже и
they don’t even say what about the production of this
даже не говорят а что про постановку это
Russian  of the federation and
российской федерации и
you know how this one is buried not by Zakharova
знаете как вот эта захоронен не захарова
who
кто
declares that
заявляет что
representatives and colonies did not suffer, that
представители и колонии не пострадали то
is, for some reason, these
есть представляете почему-то эти
ladies suffered so much linen there, the barracks will
пострадали дам столько там белья казарма
smash you represent a colony in
разнесет вы представляете колонию в
which there is no
которой
administration during the arrival of the rocket
администрации во время прилета ракеты
like a diamond, another opinion
как алмаз другое мнение
to erase the traces  torture of tears on
чтобы за стираем следы пыток слез на
another I have and we have a
другую мне есть а у нас
minister such that guys  we started
министр такое что ребята начали
cooperation and very
сотрудничество нами и очень начали
actively began to tell who is real
активно рассказываются кто есть реальный
and
и
it turns out because of this,
и получается из-за этого
listen, that is, the real one who gave
послушай то есть реальный кто отдал
real commands commands, well, why not the
реальные команды команды ну и что ж не
civilian population, not only in Azov, in
мирного населения не только в азове в
other cities, someone invest
других городах кто-то вложите
wait for the
подожди
defeat of the document, yes
поражения документа да у
we have these and it’s
нас есть вот такие да и
not profitable that we could bring, but
не выгодны что мы могли приносить а вот
who gave these to kill to kill
кто кто отдавал эти убивать убивать
between you will tell it now and so you
между расскажу это вы сейчас а так вы
come up with it, you don’t know to
придумаете получится вы не знаете этого
come up with this as a
придумывать в
result of the action in our country and
следствии действию в нашей стране и
are carried out in relation to and on employees of the
проводятся по отношению к и на служащим
pestilence  logan so you don’t know this is your
моровой логан так вы не знаете это ваше
assumption so I understand
предположение так я понимаю
you are saying that they started talking about
вы говорите что они начали говорить кто
who is talking about killing civilians so
там говорю убивать мирное население так
further the release cable and that they didn’t
дальше кабель выпуска и что не давали
testify in such a tone on the
показания так тона на
basis of which you made such a conclusion
основании чего вы сделали такой вывод
based on the fact that the investigation
на основании того что следственную
team is working for
группу работает
you just  showed the loss of the news beep
вам просто показали потери гудку новости
did you believe it really no of course on
вы в нее поверили правда нет конечно по
TV be where you learned the style from
телеку будьте откуда вы узнали стиле
where did you find out from where did you know that these are
грамм откуда откуда вы узнали что это
Russian troops,
русские войска
I’ll say I looked at the Ukrainian position
я скажу я посмотрел украинскую позицию
so I looked at the Russian one, I would
так я посмотрел российскую бы я
look at Russian military bloggers
посмотрел российских блогеров военных
too, so they say that this is the
тоже так которые говорят что это же
step that Russia did this way, and here
стёпа которые россия сделала так и а вот
you get it from well, the style of the game is a
вы откуда это берете ну стиль игра a
maze-  ing
maze-ing
where does the information come from to
откуда информация
you from her bloggers
вам от нее блогеры
there is this telegram the mask of calling
есть этот telegram the mask of calling
this he is from Moscow he fought in the
это он из москвы сам он воевал на
Donbass in the fourteenth year as a
донбассе в четырнадцатом году
volunteer so he more or less
добровольцем так он более-менее
objectively leads how he himself is Russian so
объективно ведет как он сам русский так
but he kind of tries to analyze
но он как бы старается анализировать
where the arrivals were from also that  there are
откуда были прилеты также то есть
candy wrappers to debunk toys also
фантиках бы развенчивать игрушки также
called I try I'm good andraya
зовут я стараюсь я хорошо андрая
kramatorsk this was also a Russian job well
краматорск это тоже была русской работа
where absolutely this is for cola and before the
чтож куда абсолютно это за колу и до
Russians this is a Soviet rocket.
русских это советская ракета .
Look guys you were told that Russia
посмотри ребята вам сказали что у россии
does not.  and then I even went somewhere and took
нет . а потом был даже куда и возили
points from the Russians, then a bunch at the stations we
точки у российские то куча на вокзалах
just sort it out
просто разбираем
very very simple very simple here
очень очень прост очень просто здесь
so that you have everything, whatever it is, it’s all
чтобы у вас все что ни будь это все
like a production, it’s all Ukraine
вроде постановки это все украина
was
была
drunk, [ __ ] the whole world that God
пьяна пиздил всему миру что бог [__]
didn’t [ __ ] say
не говорила
[music]
[музыка]
laughs  finds out that
смеется выясняет что
youtube u dial denis again low
youtube у наберите денису снова low
change to what and what what here from the other
смена до что а что что тут из другой
say what what here below
скажите что что вот здесь внизу
who is fired and about other things
который уволен да про другую юрмале вещи
in Jurmala we are now analyzing point situations being without being a butch in something at least in
будучи не будучи ни буча в чем-то хоть в
solo and there is a guilty one  but now we have a
соло и есть виновный но мы сейчас очень
lot of pinpoint in this military operation, the
много точечных в этой военной операции
war is going on just learn this, this
войне происходит точно выучи вот это вот
is constantly there, the Russians say that
это постоянно там русские говорят что
it is the Ukrainians who give birth to Ukrainians Russians,
это украинца украинцами рождает русские
that is, you are now saying that these are all
то есть ты сейчас говоришь что это все
Russian Russian Ukrainians are also provocations,
русские русские украинцы тоже провокации
some things
какие-то дела
look, for example, let's see who
смотрите например давайте так кто
the Kursk region of
обстреливается там курскую область
Bryansk is shelled there, respect our exchange troubles,
брянск уважь этом обменные беды наши то
it’s logical, though our shelled trick
это логично правда наш обстрелянных трюк
on the territory of Ukraine is not  neither on the
на территорию украины нет ни на
territory we will also fire at your
территории мы тоже обстреляем ваши
objects, but this is our legal right, and
объекты но это наше законное право и
but if Russia had not invaded, this
но если бы россия не вторглась этого
would not have been true, that is, of course, the
ничего не было правда то есть ну конечно
culprits of the situation server are Russia
виновников сервер ситуации есть россии
if you do not want to be found click on you
если вы не хотите чтобы на вас нашло
do not attack from very simply
щелкайте не нападайте из очень просто
when you  they climbed into someone else's house so they
когда вы залезли в чужой дом так
stole the TV and then it turns out that the
своровали телевизор а потом окажется что
prosecutor didn’t rinse the phone where the
прокурор не прополощи телефон где
thermal paste I repeat this words
термопаста я этого повторять слова
gordon of my words I don’t watch my words in vain
гордон своих слов я свои слова зря не
you feel you feel Dimka Dimka
чувствует чувствуешь у димка димка
Gordon with the second you watch Gendon yes
гордон со вторым вы смотрите гендона да
yes I am very treasures signed cool let’s
да я очень скарбом подписанные прикольно
go  it's not that I relate to him,
идем дело не в том что их к нему
I just want to understand you are a
отношусь я просто хочу понять вы
little bit serious, that is, you are allowed to
чуть-чуть серьезно то есть вам позволено
kill
убиваюсь
yourself again, look back, maybe not
еще раз смотрите вернемся может не
people again, people there are no bases, you are now a
еще раз люди там базами нет вы сейчас
manipulator, people of Donbass, these are people of
манипулятор люди донбасс это люди
Ukraine, these are citizens of Ukraine, so their
украины это граждане украины так что их
didn’t kill until I started the war there, the
не убивал пока я там не началась война
war began due to the course of the Russian
война началась из-за хода российских
militants, the capture of Slavyansk, they bent to
боевиков захвата славянска согнули
steer and  google until April 12
порулить и погуглите до 12 апреля до
before Girkin captured Slavyansk or there
того как гиркин захватил славянск или
were some casualties in the Donbass, there was no
были какие-то жертвы на донбассе не было
one
кто
good
хорошо
from military operations, no pour it
от военных действий никаких подлить это
is important this is important, we will put in this also
важно это важно мы поставим в этом тоже
grant no games no victims of
даровать никого игр никаких жертв
military conflicts until April 12 there were no victims of military conflicts on the
военных конфликтов до 12 апреля на
territory of Donbass  ukraine
территории донбаса небыло ни украина
didn’t kill anyone 8 donbass didn’t kill anyone at
никого не убивала 8 донбасс никого не
all, that is, if the Russian
убил вообще то есть если бы российское
invasion through girkin hadn’t started and
вторжение через гиркина не началась и
because of this hostilities began
из-за этого начались военных действий
because they didn’t start capturing
потому что не начали захватывать людей
people in the basement, they began to follow, for example,
людей на подвал начали следить например
in Gorlovka already on April 17 they killed a deputy of the
в горловке уже 17 апреля убили депутата
city council  elected local residents of
городского совета избранного местного
Gorlovka so because he
горловчане на так из-за того что он флаг
will return the Ukrainian flag to the flag because
украинский верну на флаг что потому что
these militants went there to
эти боевики пошли там русский
come up with a Russian take if you choose
придумать возьмите если выберете
if
если я
I look again let's
еще раз еще раз смотрите давайте
now google the murder of a deputy fisherman in the
сейчас так убийство депутата рыбака в
throat and you will see
горловке нагуглить и и вы посмотрите 17
April 17  2014, these are the first victims
апреля 2014 года вот это первые жертвы
of these military, also not in the Donbass, the
военных этих тоже не на донбассе
Russian victim before this  oh when it's the
российским жертву до этого когда это
second it's
второе это же
later
позже
let's
давайте мы
see you want to jump over
смотрите вы вы хотите перепрыгивать
time for a while let's deal with
времени на время давайте разберемся с
this time it looks like tanks at home I
этим времени выглядит танками дома я вас
asked a third of you can you name at least one
трети расспрашивал можете мне хоть одну
victim until April 12 who they
жертву назвать до до 12 апреля кого там
crushed with a tank in the Donbass were shot
со давили танком на донбассе расстреляли
there in the Donbass  but I’m explaining to you once again
там на донбассе лишь я ж вам еще раз
to catch the first first tanks
поясняю наловить первую первые танки
went on March 30 they went from 91 years old
пошли 30 марта они ходили с 91 года
tanks went
ходили танки
take it and take it to me on google and those
возьмите да возьмите мне на google и те
and tell me who Ukraine killed before
и скажите кого убила украина до 12
April 12 in the Donbas tell me
апреля на донбассе подскажите я
I was wrong so tell me let
я был неправ вот скажите давайте
's give the address
давайте адрес
can you, without tanks, here’s the last name before
можно вам без танков вот фамилию до
Crombie, is there any particular girl and
кромби ли конкретно какую-то девочка и
how many heavenly hundreds will suit you
сколько вас устроит
in that, let
небесная сотня в том давайте так вы
’s jump over in the Donbass on the
сейчас перепрыгните на донбассе на
Maidan now, let’s start
майдане сейчас начнем
again on the process, let’s then we put an
раз на процесса давайте то мы ставим
end to the fact that in the Donbass until April 12 there
точку что на донбассе до 12 апреля жертв
will be no victims  it would be such that you don’t know
не было бы таких не знаете
Ukraine in the Donbass and see the photo of the territory
украины на донбассе и фото территорию
again you say that
посмотреть еще раз вы говорите что там
Ukraine killed Donbas Borrelia there and
убивала украина боррелей донбасс и
kifato an important area different areas
kifato важной области разные области
you just residents know you are on the currency of the
вы просто жители знаете вы на валюте
system
системы на
wait a minute let's finish with the Donbass
подожди давайте закончим с донбассом
let's move on
давайте перейдем
Vela has become once again you talked about tanks
вела стал еще раз вы говорили про танки
we will put an end to the tanks that there were no
мы поставим точку в танках что никаких
victims from tanks until April 12 at all
жертв от танков до 12 апреля вообще не
there is really
было правда
no place there is no heavenly  a hundred that were
не места нет небесная сотня который
killed on the Maidan to give, they
убита на майдан давать
got them from the Donbass,
добыли из донбасса
pour them out, yes,
выльем их да
they came there to defend the
они туда приходили отстаивать
heavenly hundred, these are the people who were on the
небесная сотня это люди которые были на
Maidan, they were against Yanukovych before they
майдане они были против януковича до их
were shot by Russian snipers
потом российские снайперы расстреливали
to deliver power if you were
доставить мощь если вы были были
investigating, the locals were Russian
расследования местные были российские
alpha sheep were caught before
альф овцы были до
and  so far nothing
и до сих пор ничего до
still under investigation
сих пор идет расследование
perry jump 20 now we’ll finish from the
перри прыгайте 20 сейчас закончим с
heavenly hundred and move on to the second of May it’s
небесной сотни и перейдём ко второму мая
good to give give about the heavenly
хорошо давать давать про по небесной
hundreds it turns out they shot
сотни это получается расстреливали как
just some people from the Donbass
раз ни каких то людей там из донбасса
who were against it and it’s vice versa yes they
которые были против и это наоборот да
shot  those people who were on the
расстреливали тех людей которые были на
Maidan
майдане
steadily
неуклонно
once again
еще раз
sacrificed heaven  it’s worth hundreds it’s not a
жертву небесный стоит сотни это не
murder the murder was correctly taken away so
убийство убийство правильно увели так
who is it that Ukraine killed before people
кто это что украина убивала до людей
killed the
убивал
Russian hut Russian correctly
российской изба российские правильно
well done they did there why
молодец они там делали у вас почему что
did they also only the golden eagle I’ll say what we
делали тоже только беркут я скажу что
did while considering we asked what we
еще рассмотрении мы расспросили что
did let’s answer and what the
делали давайте отвечу а что делали
Russians did  these in Kazakhstan in January,
российские эти в казахстане в январе так
despite the fact that there
при том что
was help to
была помощь
jump over the system on the topic of
перепрыгивать система на тему
what was like why Russia is Russia
что было типа почему россия это россия
interfering in the
вмешивается в
process and in neighboring states
процесс и в соседних государства
who he is in my opinion all the good ones who are
кто он по моему все хорошие кто такая
here
тут
asked him to be pressed and
просили его прижали и
now we will build
теперь построим
you betrayed someone
вы кого-то предали
to give someone to ukraine
вы кого-то придать украина
so yes to this white drunk I don’t
да так в этот белый пьяный меня нет
you don’t want to say you are no hybrids
вы не хотите сказать вы никого гибридами
and whom we gave
а кого мы придали
you all the people ukraine betrayed and the
вы весь народ украину предали и
ukrainian people we gave the ukrainian
украинский народ мы придали украинский
people the completely
народа совершенно
ukrainian people betrayed themselves on and in the
украинский народ сам себя предал на у и
sense the ukrainian people this bunch  a gang of
всмысле украинский народ эта кучка шайка
people who were standing there on Independence Square,
людей которые там стояли на площади
this is being read by the Ukrainian
незалежности это читает украинским
people there by a
народом там
representative  ukrainian people
представитель украинского народа
500000 up to a million
500000 до миллиона
rallies are allowed in ukraine so in ukraine people were
разрешены митинги так в украине народ
looking for what we immediately allowed
искал что сразу у нас за разрешены
boucle rallies in ukraine we have in
митинга букле в украине у нас
short you are a cosmonaut
короче вы космонавт
in russia you can’t gather at a rally but
в россии нельзя собираться на митинге а
in ukraine you can and we have been going for years and
в украине можно и мы годами собирались и
when something doesn’t  we liked it,
когда на что-то не нравилось мы выходили
it’s for us
на митинги это для нас
to kill the guys the golden eagle no no no look
убить парней беркут нет нет нет смотрите
because of what the clashes began the golden eagle
из-за чего начались столкновения беркут
began to beat people before there were only
начал избивать людей до было только были
clashes and that he
столкновения и что
starts throwing stones at look, I understand
начинает кидать камни в смотри я понимаю
that, for example, you, for example, you
что а вы например вы в украинской
understood Ukrainian politics better than
политике разбиралась лучше чем
Russian on a nipple I can
российской на ниппель могу
generally
вообще
Russia knows Ukraine very well
россия очень хорошо
you violated 390 in one day,
украину вы за один день нарушили
on the basis of which you decided to eat
390 она на основании чего вы решили есть
here we have a cassation court body
вот у нас есть кассационный суд орган
that decides
который решает нарушенного было
whether the constitution was violated or not you have some kind of
конституции или нет у вас есть какое-то
decision we take a number I find an antivirus
решение берем число нахожу антивирус
tell us about  I will say let's first
расскажите про скажу давайте первый
moment you are suspended by the law on
момент вы отстранены закон об
education who
образовании кто
am I on the
я по
second education let me here  very
второе образование давайте я вот очень
very very carefully immediately let's go
очень и очень внимательно сразу давайте
2 1 1 no
по 2 1 1 нет образование
diploma education legal
диплома юридической
technical officially the
техническая официально
first moment officially
первый момент официально
unofficially
неофициально
there is a decision
есть решение
for some reason on the basis of what you say
почему-то на основании чего вы говорите
here you are sitting you asked a question listen
вот вы сидите вы задали вопрос послушай
not now the branches you are sitting my cute why are
не теперь ветви вы сидя my cute почему
you haiti what is this  not anti-constitutional,
ты гаити что это не антиконституционный
look, we have such a constitutional
смотрите у нас есть по конституции такой
body as the constitutional court, if the
орган как конституционный суд если
state body is the supreme council, the
государственный орган верховный совет
president or the cabinet, and even issues
президент или кабмин и даже издает
some kind of decree, a decision and a decision
какой-то указ решение и постановление
that does not comply with the constitution,
которое не соответствует конституции
other bodies can file a
другие органы могут подать
constitutional court with this time to
конституционный суд с этим раз тумане
explain in the fog whether this
разъяснить или соответствует эта
constitution complies  and we only had,
конституция и у нас бывал только
for example, the case for this decision, the screen
например дело к это постановление скрин
court analyzes and reports that it does not
суд разбирает и доносит что она не
correspond to the cast, so we
соответствует кастуется поэтому нам
need to be canceled so if you
нужно быть отменено так если вы
claim that this decision of the
утверждаете что это постановление
supreme council was not
верховного совета было не кассационным
cassation, then show me the appeal to the
так то покажите мне обращение в
constitutional court the decision of the
конституционный суд решение
constitutional  about the courts of such no world
конституционного суда таких не мировой
no one fifty-fifty percent of the
никто пятьдесят на пятьдесят процентов
people were removed immediately
людей убрали сразу
immediately
сразу
flowed again into the ring, for example, if
потекли еще раз в кольцо например если
you think that Yanukovych was wrong, he
вы считаете что янукович неправильно он
applied to the constitutional court
обращался в конституционный суд
to turn to
обратиться к чему
what exactly because of the fact that he left the
вот вот именно из за того что он покинул
territory of Ukraine because  of this, and the
территорию украины из-за этого и
supreme council
верховный совет
turns out to be the supreme council, this is a
получается верховный совет это
legitimate body, this is a deputy elected by the people of the
легитимный орган это избранный людьми
ice, look here if
депутат льда у нас смотрите у нас если
you know the Ukrainian constitution so and
вы знаете украинскую конституцию так и
that is, here is the
то есть вот
legislative body, the power is so and
законодательный орган власть так и
if there is no president, then he is the head of the supreme
если нету президента то глава верховного
council, he is acting
совета он есть исполняющим обязанности
correctly, the explosion first 20  February
правильно взрыв сначал 20 февраля еще
once again think like a lawyer once again if you
раз еще раз мыслить как юрист если вы
or someone else think that it
или кто-то и другой считаю что это была
was unconstitutional, show the document in
не конституционно покажите документ в
which the constitutional court was filed about the
котором подавалась конституционный суд о
unconstitutionality of this action or
неконституционности этого действия или
or that someone of some body made a
или что кто-то какой-то орган вынес
revision to the sun that it was some kind of
доработкой солнцу что это была некая
he is holy now it’s only your words that the
свят он сейчас это только ваши слова
deputies called so who voted  for
звали депутаты так которые голосовали за
this decision, including from the Party of
это решение в том числе из партии
Regions, from the Communists from Donetsk,
регионов из коммунистов из донецкой
deputies from Luhansk, and then why did they
депутаты из луганской и тогда чего они
all vote for this decision, before that
все голосовали за вот это решение до что
zinc removed
цинковый самоустранился
you on TV, well, now there are also debates
вас по телеку ну тоже сейчас идут дебаты
there, so tell captcha over
там стоят так рассказывать captcha над
to do here in Russia  so the
сделать вот у нас в россии так постоянно
theta of the engine is constantly going on
тета движка идет
and we are now also watching the same garbage
и мы сейчас также следим такая же [__]
like this, at least someone sees a trick
как вот это хоть кто-то видит выходок
that solves these questions in general how
тот решает вообще эти вопросы как
to make the account end or just
сделать чтоб счет закончилась или просто
like that everyone is procrastinating in this hat don’t
так же все мусолят в этот шляпу не
consider how we
рассмотрите как у нас общественная
always have a public discussion  we are now experiencing
дискуссия всегда нет у нас сейчас идет
guilt, we understand that in order for this to end like this, it
вина мы понимаем что для того чтобы это
is necessary to drive the Russian
закончилось так надо прогнать российские
troops out of the queen’s friend, this will not
войска из у queen другом это не
end, no peace
закончится ника никакого мирного
agreement, what we eat there, parts of history
соглашения что мы ем там части истории
will not be, this Ukrainian society will not
не будем это украинское общество это не
perceive it, so in any configuration,
воспримет так ни в каких конфигурациях
let's go there  we will give this region this
давайте там эту область отдадим эту
Adyghe, that is, the state and the people, this is
адыги то есть государство и народ это
on purpose, I am at an impasse,
нарочно я в тупике
you do not give in to this, and because  oh,
вы нет в этом уступить и потому что рано
or later, these military resources will run out of you,
или поздно вас закончатся ресурс эти так
and yet Russia will have
военные и все-таки россия должна будет
to retreat the road, I think the tsarist one
отступить дорогу думаю царской
will end, but I’m helping us,
закончится а нам помогаю вот
look at the economy of Russia, the economy of the
посмотрите экономику россии экономику
states, the raw materials of the European Union, before
штатов сырье евросоюза до
that, for a narrow moment, Russia cost a small,
что узкому миг россию стоил на маленький
small,
маленький
therefore, people, people in America, they are richer
поэтому люди люди в америке они богаче
than people  in russia than people in ukraine
чем люди в россии чем люди в украине
because there
потому что там
is a salary in america salary in yakutia
зарплата в америке зарплата в якутии
contagious
заразные
salary can you read in a clearing that
зарплату может вы читали на поляну то
is, you think that the
есть вы считаете что
car in yakutia tops in america where the
машина в якутии вершинам в америке где
car is 10 and although of course, well, what
машину и хотя конечно ну тут еще какое
quality is the
качество
same as a foreign car, for example, for this
одинаковое иномарку так например ибо это
let’s find the deer skin for half an hour we’ve been talking
давайте найдем уже полчаса говорим
finished, I realized that in America it’s cheaper than a
закончен я понял что в америке дешевле
car in Yakutia, it’s cheaper than deer skins,
машины в якутии дешевле шкуры оленей на
I didn’t wait half an hour on this, I’m already tired of
не подождала полчаса я я уже замучился
saying let me run for a
говорит давать я побегу на
deer skin in America, how much they cost
[__] оленя в америке сколько не стоят
cheaper
они дешевле
[music]
[музыка]
I can’t be kind  I think here and so all the
меня не можем добрым думаю тут и так все
bachyls up to
бачылы до
the one on the side of the scalar will be absolutely
той что сбоку скалярно будем абсолютно
routes such braids follow the norm  flax
трассы такие тесьмы следовать нормально
here is bruce and the ears of the back of the system’s nikitushka
вот брюс и ушки спина никитушке системы
on topics to shoot, but here the whole length from and
на темы стрелять но сюда всю длину от и
but all his arguments
но все его аргументы
are broken about real facts oh yes you are about
разбиваются о реальные факты о да ты о
some events of the chronology so and when
какие-то события хронологии так и когда
he sees that he’s not getting it yet and
он видит что не получая он еще и
forward it to another detailed one
переправить на другой собой детальный
parsing it is another so to my shovels the whole
разбор она другое так моему лопаты всю
school and save yourself on the channel put likes
школу и спасайтесь на канал ставте лайки
there comments stole the defeat of the
там комментарии похитили поражение цикле
dashi cycle so with the face well, after all, we
даси так with the face ну все-таки
change the children examined with frequent although the
меняем детьми исследованы с частыми хотя
dishes and so I think they even chatted 2
блюда и так я думаю даже болтали 2
marvel at the sight and the cape on and the workshop and
дивляться виду и накидку на и цеху и
way mouse all swear glory glue
шлях мышки all ругаемся славу клей